# Basit Ali



alib4111@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/basit-ali-04a790151



+923087310740



https://www.codingwithbasit.com

### Summary

I am an experienced Web Developer with more than 4 years of experience building web applications using different technologies. I have vast experience in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, React, NodeJs, Express, MongoDB, GraphQL, and also in relational databases.

I am a freelance web developer currently. With coding experience, I also have experience of teaching students across the globe. I have taught almost 400 students from different countries across the globe all online.

### **Experience**



#### Freelance Web Developer

Jun 2019 - Present (3 years 8 months)

Front-end Intern at Red Signal Software Company, Lahore.

## **Chief Executive Officer at bobisoft**

bobisoft

Sep 2020 - Present (2 years 5 months)

I created this company. My company servers businesses by giving software solutions of almost all kinds.

## Freelance Web Developer

Fivver.com

Mar 2019 - Present (3 years 11 months)

# .NET Developer

**PRINTMIS** 

Jul 2019 - Apr 2020 (10 months)

if you know how to code, you can, no matter what the syntax is.

#### **Education**



### Bahauddin Zakariya University

Master of Computer Science, Computer Science

2016 - 2018

I am a freelance web developer having experience in WordPress, HTML, ¡Query, JavaScript, CSS and Bootstrap. I work on www.fiverr.com. If you want your business to grow and nurture in good pace then contact me I would help you in the best possible way by developing very-helpful websites for your organization.

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

# $\hat{\mathbf{U}}$ Build Responsive Real World Websites with HTML and CSS - Udemy

### **Skills**

React.js • Node.js • Express.js • JavaScript • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • REST APIs • GraphQL • MongoDB • SQL